I hope I didn't scare you with this really heavy gear video.
I have a new silicone product I want to show you today.
Maybe you've seen the videos in which I've worn multiple silicone catsuits from Urania or Smitherson.
If not, check them out.
And I have something new from Smitherson. They released a special silicone mask.
I'm going to show it to you because the style is really, really special.
special it's basically a gas mask style some heavy gear and I'm going to tell you more about it now
as with all these silicone products the mask is quite heavy too and it's quite thick I'd say
around about four millimeter thick and you can also see that on the inside there is this medicine
logo imprinted it's kind of cool there are different layers to it so they glued these
It evolves into the mask for a rather seamless look. And we have this kind of fabric structure on the inside so it doesn't tear especially behind the lacing part.
and the glasses are also integrated into the mask and I can try to show you who
what you can see through these glasses they are some kind of tinted glass and I
think it adds to the overall dark look that these are tinted it's really sturdy
so if I hold it like this you can see that it holds the shape and it's really
sturdy it does not wobble around too much so that is also a comparison or a
difference to latex like this is really thick and sturdy whereas latex as the
outfit I'm wearing is rather thin and that's also a special feature of
silicone to have this more enclosed and thicker feeling you can order it with
different accessories and these are best shown on a hat. Welcome to my lovely
assistant you can suggest some names in the comments but it's easier for me to
show the function to you like this so the front part here is super squishy
it's a softer silicone than the rest there is no function to this so this is
purely for optical reason. The functional ones are here on the sides. There are actual holes in them.
I can insert my fingers so you can breathe through them. And now you can order it with different
accessories. Of course you can also use your own gear which you already have at home but this is a
standard M40 thread and there is no matching thread on the inside here but the silicone is so
soft that you can actually just basically push it inside and it works and it fits. Also part of the
standard accessory range is this re-breathing bag and the Y part here which you can use in various
weight and as for shining it up please use the Smidison silicon shiner they
offer in their shop and they sent this to you if you order something made of
silicon it's safer that way so please don't just use anything but this I hope
this video was helpful because there are new items but I didn't see a lot of
pictures or even videos with them online so if you like this one check out just
medicine shop there's a lot to explore and I also have a discount code with
which you can save some money so check it out in the description text I'll link
everything and I hope you aren't scared or I didn't scare you with this really
heavy gear video but I thought since everyone loved the silicon catsuits and
everyone was really really interested in this silicon material let's show you
some more of what Smidazen and their sister company Rorania are able to do
it's really interesting topic so again if you want to learn more check out the
homepage and I think I'm done here I hope you had a nice time and I will see
you in the next video see you around bye